# Nicholas Nall

120 Sea Salt Ln, Ocean Springs, MS

Phone: (228) 334-9173 | Email nicholas.nall@gmail.com

#### Junior Front-End Developer with a passion for creating intuitive, beautiful, and durable design.

Self-taught/teaching for two years, with proficiency in HTML, CSS & JS, responsive website and web app creation, and API integration. Seeking full-time junior level position to continue bettering these skills and gain experience.

## **EDUCATION**

B.A., Political Science, Louisiana State University, 2012

### LINKS

github.com/nnall

codepen.io/nnall 

codepen.io/nnall

codepen.io/nnall

in linkedin.com/in/nicholas-nall-0b3795252/

## SKILLS

Front-End	Back-End	Source- Control	JavaScript Libraries	Other Libraries	Other
HTML5	JavaScript	Git	Leaflet.js	Lottie-Js	Node Package Manager (NPM)
CSS3	Node.js	GitHub	GreenSock (GSAP)	Bootstrap	Photoshop
Node Sass/ SCSS			FullPage.js		Figma

## **WORK HISTORY**

Position/Company	Duties	Technologies
Musician / Nick Nall Music	Group/Solo music entertainment in and around Ocean Springs, MS	Heart, soul
Database Admin / Cooper Law Firm (2019-20)	Managed discovery/evidence & client profile databases for large class action lawsuits Secured and produced digital evidence Assisted in software migrations, data import/export Served as general I.T.	Nextpoint eDiscovery, Clio Client Intake Mgmt NetDocuments Records Mgmt Microsoft Outlook, Excel
Inventory Manager / IDScan.net (2018-19)	Inventory management and orders/returns, tracking all customers POs, managing several online sales channels	SKU-Vault Inventory Mgmt, 3D-Cart eCommerce, Microsoft Access, Excel
Airport Operations / Gulfport Int'l Airport (2016-18)	Maintained federal compliance pursuant to airport safety & security, federal regulation Daily inspections, issuing work orders, purchase orders Handled employee onboarding, training, security clearances.	